* Select a Region 
    
    * * *

    * * *

FREE US SHIPPING on all orders $75+

* Select a Region 
    
    * * *

    * * *

* 

[Home](https://en.j5create.com/ "Home") | Privacy Policy | j5create

#### **j5create PRIVACY POLICY**

j5create ("j5create," "we," "our," or "us") understands and appreciates the importance of privacy to our customers. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we may obtain and how we may use and disclose that information. We also explain the choices available to you regarding our use of the information, the steps we take to safeguard the information, and how you how may contact us if you have any questions about our privacy practices.

**Information We Obtain**

When using or purchasing a j5create product or use a j5create service ("Product" or "Products"), we may receive from you one or more of the following:

1. contact information, such as name, email address, postal address and phone number;
2. internet protocol address;
3. information about your browser or operating system;
4. payment card information (including name, card number, expiration date and security code);
5. user coupon or gift card number;
6. date of birth;
7. gender;
8. username and password for participating third-party devices, apps, features or services;
9. information you store on your device, such as photos, contacts, text logs, touch interactions, settings and calendar information;
10. location data.

We may obtain certain information about you from publicly or commercially-available sources and from third parties who perform services for us. We also may obtain other information about you, your devices and your use of the Products, in ways we describe at the time we collect the information or otherwise with your consent.

**What we do with your information**

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates. Through certain of the Products, both we and various third parties may collect information about your online activities to provide you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. We may also use the information to provide and enhance our Products, such as registering you or your device, identifying and authenticating you so you may use and interact with third-party services, and improving and customizing your experience. We may also use the information to provide customer support, evaluate and operate our business, identify and protect against fraud, and comply with any applicable laws.

**Information Sharing**

We may share your personal information with service providers who perform services for us. We do not authorize our service providers to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. 

**Age of Consent**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.  Unless otherwise specified, the Products and information provided by j5create (including any j5create website or social media account) are designed for a general audience and are not directed to children. In connection with the Products, we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, upon notification and verification, we will either seek parental consent or promptly delete that information. If you believe that a child under age 13 may have provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us.

**Links to Other Websites, Devices, Apps and Features**

The Products may provide the ability to connect to websites, devices, apps and other features, which may operate independently from us and may have their own privacy notices or policies. We strongly suggest you review them. To the extent any linked website, device, app or other feature is not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for its content, use, or privacy practices.

**Shopify**

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.  
Payment: If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted. All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers. For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

**Third Party Services**

In general, to our knowledge, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So, if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service. When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**Security**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with an AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we attempt to follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**Cookies**

Here is a list of a majority of the cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.  
\_kla\_id, unique token, sessional, Tracks clicks through the emails to the Shopify store.  
KL\_FORMS\_MODAL, unique token, indefinite if the shop has an email, Tracks subscription (opts in) to a form.  
Facebook Custom Audience: Deliver ads on Facebook to a certain group of users.  
Google AdSense: Display advertisements to you based on your interests.  
Google AdWords Conversion: Better understand how effective our digital campaigns are.  
Google Analytics: Collect information about how visitors use our website.  
Google Dynamic Remarketing: Track user behavior over time and across third party sites to improve the effectiveness of our online advertising.  
Google Tag Manager: Track user behavior, traffic analysis and marketing optimization.  
Pinterest: Enable social sharing buttons on our sites, as well as to track social media and other Web browsing behavior in order to target ads and promotions to your interests. For information about how to opt-out of Pinterest cookies, visit [here](https://help.pinterest.com/en/article/personalization-and-data).  
Twitter, Inc. and Twitter Button: Enable social sharing buttons on our sites, as well as to track social media and other Web browsing behavior in order to target ads and promotions to your interests. For information on how to opt-out of Twitter, visit [here](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies).  
YouTube Video Tracking: Measure user engagement with our videos in order to improve our marketing and support video content.

**How to Contact Us**

If you would like to: access, correct, withdraw your consent, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@j5create.com or by mail at  
j5create  
Re: Data Protection Officer  
1025 Cobb International Drive, Suite 210  
Kennesaw, Georgia US 30152

**Notice to California Residents**

**1\. Notice of Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We may collect the following categories of personal information about you:

* **Identifiers**: identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier (such as a device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers and similar technology; customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias; telephone number and other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers), online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, and other similar identifiers
* **Additional Data Subject to Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80**: signature, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, and other financial information
* **Protected Classifications**: characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as age and sex
* **Commercial Information**: commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, and other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
* **Biometric Information**
* **Online Activity**: Internet and other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with websites, applications or advertisements
* **Geolocation Data**
* **Sensory Information**: audio, electronic, visual, and similar information
* **Inferences**: inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes.
* **Prior Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

We may have collected and used your personal information, as described in Section 1 above, during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this California Consumer Privacy Statement. For the personal information collected during that timeframe, we describe below: (a) the categories of sources from which we may have obtained the personal information, (b) the categories of third parties with whom we may have shared the information, (c) the categories of personal information we may have sold, and (d) the categories of personal information we may have disclosed for a business purpose.

**2\. Sources of Personal Information**

We may have obtained personal information about you from various sources, including:

* from you or your devices, for example, through your use of the Products;
* vendors who provide services on our behalf;
* social media networks; and
* online advertising companies. 

**3\. Sharing of Personal Information**

We may have shared your personal information with certain categories of vendors, including:

* vendors who provide services on our behalf;
* professional services organizations, such as auditors and law firms;
* our joint marketing partners;
* our business partners;
* advertising networks;
* internet service providers;
* data analytics providers;
* government entities;
* operating systems and platforms;
* social networks; and
* consumer data resellers.

**4\. Sale of Personal Information**

We may allow certain third parties (such as advertising partners) to collect your personal information. You have the right to opt out of this disclosure of your information.  During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this California Consumer Privacy Statement, we may have sold the following categories of personal information:

* Identifiers such as a unique personal identifier (such as a device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers and similar technology; other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers), online identifier, and internet protocol address
* Commercial information, including records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, and other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
* Internet and other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with websites, applications or advertisements
* Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes.

**5\. Disclosure of Personal Information for a Business Purpose**

We may have disclosed to vendors the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:

* Identifiers such as a real name, postal address, telephone number, unique personal identifier (such as a device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers and similar technology; customer number; other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers), online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, and other similar identifiers
* Signature, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number and other financial information
* Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as age and sex
* Commercial information, including records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, and other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
* Internet and other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with websites, applications or advertisements
* Geolocation Data
* Audio, electronic, visual and similar information
* Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes. 

**California Consumer Privacy Rights**

You have certain choices regarding our use and disclosure of your personal information, as described below.

**Access**: You may have the right to request, twice in a 12-month period, that we disclose to you the personal information we have collected, used, disclosed and sold about you during the past 12 months.

**Deletion**: You have the right to request that we delete certain personal information we have collected from you.

**Opt-Out of Sale**: You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information.

**Shine the Light Request**: You also may have the right to request that we provide you with (1) a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (2) the identity of those third parties.

**Verifying Requests**: To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your personal information or complying with your request. If you have a j5create account, we will verify your identity by requiring you to sign in to your account. If you do not have a j5create account, or an email address on file with us, then there is no reasonable method by which we can verify your identity to the level of certainty required by the CCPA.  Accordingly, if you do not have an account with us, or an email address on file, and you request access to or deletion of your personal information, we will not be able to process your request at this time.

**Additional Information**: If you choose to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by us. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request.

###### INFO

###### PRODUCTS

###### SUPPORT

###### CONNECT

Sign up for the latest innovations, exclusive offers, and more.

SUBSCRIBE

* * *

* * *

Copyright © 2024 [j5create](https://en.j5create.com/)

All trademarks and trade names may be used in this document to refer to either the entities claiming the marks and/or names or their products and are the property of their respective owners. All company, product and service names used are for identification purposes only. Use of these names, logos, and brands does not imply endorsement. We disclaim any interest in the marks of others. [Learn more >](https://en.j5create.com/pages/attribution-statements)

[© 2024 j5create](https://en.j5create.com/) • [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)
